<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-03-08T22:56:39+11:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Chaithanya Gunturi</title><subtitle></subtitle><entry><title type="html">Service Victoria</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/03/25/Service-Victoria.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Service Victoria" /><published>2019-03-25T00:00:00+11:00</published><updated>2019-03-25T00:00:00+11:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/03/25/Service-Victoria</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/03/25/Service-Victoria.html"><![CDATA[<p>Managed multiple web and mobile development team &amp; delivered several complex releases successfully acrss various clients.</p>

<p><strong><em>Roles and Responsibilities</em></strong></p>

<ul>
  <li>Leading a delivery team in the execution of Agile Software projects</li>
  <li>Working with client/customer to understand the requirements and define technical solutions</li>
  <li>Working with other Delivery Leads to perform impact analysis on key initiatives</li>
  <li>Development team – guiding the team through the analysis, design, development, testing and implementation phases</li>
  <li>Making sure to eliminate the obstacles and the problems which prevent the team from moving forward and from progressing in its work</li>
  <li>Assisting with internal and external communication, improving transparency, and radiating information</li>
  <li>Ensuring customer satisfaction targets were always met</li>
  <li>Supporting and educating the Product Owner, especially with respect to refining / grooming and managing the product backlog</li>
  <li>Working closely with the Lead Designer on product designs and make contributions to architectural issues where possible</li>
  <li>Coordinating with release management &amp; QA to ensure smooth release processes are maintained</li>
  <li>Managing delivery of a cross functional software delivery team</li>
  <li>Providing timely updates to management</li>
  <li>Establishing program level cadence and driving program level ceremonies (e.g. PI Planning, release train retrospectives, backlog refinement)</li>
  <li>Prioritizing and managing own workload and the workload of team members to deliver quality results and meet timelines</li>
  <li>Line management of team members and their professional development</li>
  <li>Monitor and track status of iterations/releases and ensure work progress visualization on the scrum board</li>
  <li>Responsible for defining processes as part of scaling up agile teams &amp; successfully implemented Scrum in 10+ teams</li>
  <li>Responsible for maintaining JIRA/Confluence, Miro, Slack, Trello, Postman Pro</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managed multiple web and mobile development team &amp; delivered several complex releases successfully acrss various clients. Roles and Responsibilities Leading a delivery team in the execution of Agile Software projects Working with client/customer to understand the requirements and define technical solutions Working with other Delivery Leads to perform impact analysis on key initiatives Development team – guiding the team through the analysis, design, development, testing and implementation phases Making sure to eliminate the obstacles and the problems which prevent the team from moving forward and from progressing in its work Assisting with internal and external communication, improving transparency, and radiating information Ensuring customer satisfaction targets were always met Supporting and educating the Product Owner, especially with respect to refining / grooming and managing the product backlog Working closely with the Lead Designer on product designs and make contributions to architectural issues where possible Coordinating with release management &amp; QA to ensure smooth release processes are maintained Managing delivery of a cross functional software delivery team Providing timely updates to management Establishing program level cadence and driving program level ceremonies (e.g. PI Planning, release train retrospectives, backlog refinement) Prioritizing and managing own workload and the workload of team members to deliver quality results and meet timelines Line management of team members and their professional development Monitor and track status of iterations/releases and ensure work progress visualization on the scrum board Responsible for defining processes as part of scaling up agile teams &amp; successfully implemented Scrum in 10+ teams Responsible for maintaining JIRA/Confluence, Miro, Slack, Trello, Postman Pro]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Vicroads</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/11/01/VicRoads.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vicroads" /><published>2018-11-01T00:00:00+11:00</published><updated>2018-11-01T00:00:00+11:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/11/01/VicRoads</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/11/01/VicRoads.html"><![CDATA[<p>Worked on a project to migrate the print house from existing solution to new platform. This involved working with Multiple development team vendors and a test team of 4 people.</p>

<p><strong><em>Roles and Responsibilities</em></strong></p>

<ul>
  <li>Taking full responsibility for all phases of testing and the management of the testing activities within a development and complex project</li>
  <li>Defining and owning testing component project plans, fully understand all project and testing assumptions, dependencies, and associated risks</li>
  <li>Defining and maintaining the testing strategy and various test plans. This should cover both automation and manual testing</li>
  <li>Undertaking project test estimating, planning &amp; tracking, monitoring, and reporting for the delivery of a test plan against the overall project plan</li>
  <li>Leading the design of Functional Testcases for all test phases incl. Revenue Manager feature level testing, SYS, INT, UAT and PVT</li>
  <li>Coordinating of development of automated Test Cases</li>
  <li>Managing the test preparation phases to produce test effort, resource calculation, test data, test cases, test execution plans, and defect report life cycle flows (it is essential to set up for each- project as developers use different life cycles)</li>
  <li>Providing direction and guidance for test process improvements</li>
  <li>Regulating and co-ordinating testing processes and standards across multiple and simultaneous projects and departments, for various browsers, countries, and mobile devices</li>
  <li>Writing, implementing, and reporting status for system test cases for testing</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worked on a project to migrate the print house from existing solution to new platform. This involved working with Multiple development team vendors and a test team of 4 people.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Deloitte Digital</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/11/01/Deloitte-Digital.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Deloitte Digital" /><published>2017-11-01T00:00:00+11:00</published><updated>2017-11-01T00:00:00+11:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2017/11/01/Deloitte-Digital</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2017/11/01/Deloitte-Digital.html"><![CDATA[<p>Working with multiple client and multiple projects to successfully delivery projects within committed timeframes &amp; budget</p>

<p><strong><em>Roles and Responsibilities</em></strong></p>

<ul>
  <li>Manages Project Management functional scope and schedule. Provides oversight of management and allocation of personnel and resources to projects. Resolves resource conflicts and priorities</li>
  <li>Responsible for project communications and meeting facilitation. Leads definition and measurement of success metrics to objectively quantify project success</li>
  <li>Provide overall development project leadership, and direct project teams in the delivery of high-quality products within committed timeframes &amp; budget</li>
  <li>Provide status reporting to Senior Management</li>
  <li>Works with development leads to define code drops and coordinates the alignment of code drop dependencies</li>
  <li>Builds and maintains a cohesive project team and foster working relationships</li>
  <li>Ensure effective handoff to operations for ongoing maintenance and troubleshooting</li>
  <li>Manage release night activities</li>
  <li>Manage the pipeline of work and agree priorities with key stakeholders</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working with multiple client and multiple projects to successfully delivery projects within committed timeframes &amp; budget]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Deloitte digital</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2014/08/01/Deloitte-Digital.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Deloitte digital" /><published>2014-08-01T00:00:00+10:00</published><updated>2014-08-01T00:00:00+10:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2014/08/01/Deloitte%20Digital</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2014/08/01/Deloitte-Digital.html"><![CDATA[<p>Worked on end-to-end test delivery across multiple projects while managing a team located in multiple geographic location.</p>

<p><strong><em>Roles and Responsibilities</em></strong></p>

<ul>
  <li>Managing a team of quality engineers/analysts who are tasked to identify, develop, create, and improve technical testing process/frameworks</li>
  <li>Managing both in-house and vendor testing teams by ensuring clear alignment and communication</li>
  <li>Collaborate and partner closely with program managers, development leads, test leads and production support teams to ensure that software is tested to highest quality</li>
  <li>Providing input to the project plan/release plan, defect/change management processes, systems integration, testing tools and processes</li>
  <li>Development and management of program metrics</li>
  <li>Drive continuous monitoring and improvement to testing tools and methodologies to increase test quality and effectiveness</li>
  <li>Managing development of automated test tools/test frameworks</li>
  <li>Prepare testing results for Operations Leads and Risk &amp; Control for testing sign off</li>
  <li>Foster a spirit of innovation and collaboration regarding testing</li>
  <li>Responsible for line management, include performance and career development, of QA team</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worked on end-to-end test delivery across multiple projects while managing a team located in multiple geographic location.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wipro Technologies</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2010/08/01/Wipro-Technologies.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wipro Technologies" /><published>2010-08-01T00:00:00+10:00</published><updated>2010-08-01T00:00:00+10:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2010/08/01/Wipro-Technologies</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2010/08/01/Wipro-Technologies.html"><![CDATA[<p>Worked on Multiple projects in an onshore-offshore team model and successfully delivered multiple projects</p>

<p><strong><em>Roles and Responsibilities</em></strong></p>

<ul>
  <li>Manage and lead the testing team in the planning, execution, and reporting of user acceptance testing activities to ensure that the results of a complex enterprise software development using a combination of Agile &amp; iterative methodologies</li>
  <li>Analyses patterns of defects for projects &amp; communicates findings to facilitate continual improvement</li>
  <li>Assist Test Manager with testing assignments and reporting up to client management</li>
  <li>Design and execute test plans, scenarios, scripts and procedures</li>
  <li>Develop and maintain quality assurance metrics</li>
  <li>Establish regular checkpoints and testing during the development effort</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worked on Multiple projects in an onshore-offshore team model and successfully delivered multiple projects]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ibm</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2007/10/01/IBM.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ibm" /><published>2007-10-01T00:00:00+10:00</published><updated>2007-10-01T00:00:00+10:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2007/10/01/IBM</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2007/10/01/IBM.html"><![CDATA[<p>Worked in an onshore-offshore team model and was responsible for day-to-day testing activities (test case creation, execution, defect lifecycle)</p>

<p><strong><em>Roles and Responsibilities</em></strong></p>

<ul>
  <li>Understand the various Testing processes and terminologies</li>
  <li>Test Data Management using ALM</li>
  <li>Communicate efficiently with the Onsite team (verbal and written)</li>
  <li>Conduct peer reviews</li>
  <li>Create manual test scripts for testing the application across different testing cycles</li>
  <li>Execution and Maintenance of these test scripts</li>
  <li>Interact with a team of both on and offshore test analysts, project managers, developers within team</li>
  <li>Seek and respond to development feedback</li>
  <li>Under the supervision of the Test Manager, participate in planning</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worked in an onshore-offshore team model and was responsible for day-to-day testing activities (test case creation, execution, defect lifecycle)]]></summary></entry></feed>